Introducing ladies and gentlemen, children and senior ladies in the crowd
this just in an English pod production
featuring the award nominee Marco Mejia Magia Magia
and his sidekick Leonardo Guerriero
Hello!
And me, and Marco, and Marco
So, by the way, did I spell your surnames wrong enough?
Well, yeah. Very well.
Very well. Next?
Yeah, you got it right the first time though.
So, how are you?
Very good. Thank you.
Welcome to another edition of This Just In
and we're going to be looking at next week's lessons first
so let's not delay it and let's start with lesson on Monday.
We're looking for an apartment, all right?
So we're going to be teaching you how to describe an apartment
with a walk-in closet in an unsweet bathroom and all that good stuff.
You know that a friend of mine actually, when he went to Bologna
and looked for an apartment, this guy showed him around
and then took the deposit and then disappeared?
Really?
He came back with it and he gave it the keys, no?
So he used the keys, he went back with all this stuff,
he tried to move in and they were like, he entered
and there was a bunch of people saying, like,
what are you doing here?
Nah.
Incredible, huh?
Nah, you're lying.
No, no, no. True, true, true.
What is this in Bologna?
In Bologna.
Bologna is a city.
So they went to dry eventually.
Hey, I remember you told me your bathroom doesn't have a door.
It only has a curtain.
Your bathroom is like in the middle of your living room.
No, it's your brain that is in the middle of something else.
What are you saying?
My bathroom has a door.
Yeah, my toilet has a door.
Is it your brain which is in the middle of your...
Seriously?
I hear you, Marco, you live with another 12 equatorians
in the same apartment.
Yeah, we...
That's why you don't sleep and you can...
Equatorios.
We have what we call hotbeds.
So basically, since they work different shifts,
you know, I'll sleep from, you know, 10 p.m. to 5 a.m.
and then the guy that finishes his shift
will come in at 5.30 and take my bed and...
That's a good system.
Yeah, we save money, yeah.
Yeah, it's good.
Ecologically.
Yeah, yeah, you know.
What about your toilet, Leo?
It's a very special toilet.
Oh, by the way, so we have a listener today
in the studio Liliana is in the audience.
This just in, being filmed for in a live studio audience.
Can you cheer for us, please?
We have a fan.
Yeah, we have a fan.
Just one.
But yeah, I heard that you share your apartment
with a small hairy creature.
Yeah, it's called a rabbit.
Oh, rabbit.
I thought it was Ross.
Yeah, I was talking about Ross.
No, he's quite big.
So what are you going to talk about in this lesson?
Well, yeah, we're going to be looking for an apartment.
We're going to be talking about the kitchen and appliances
and rooms and how to describe all this
and what Elise is and how to negotiate your contract.
Do you remember to check the shower
with the hot water and thing?
And remember to check behind the curtains,
make sure there isn't any mold.
Check below in the couch, like lift the cushions.
There might be money on it.
Even though every time that I find like in the pocket
of the jacket that I haven't wore in a year,
I always find like a half a sandwich.
You never find math.
But it's so cool when you find money after like one year.
Yeah, never happens to me.
It happened to me once.
I found a sandwich, half a sandwich.
What do you have sugar in your pocket?
Next lesson.
All right.
On Wednesday, we're going to be talking about Star Trek.
So we have one of those science fiction.
You can't say I know.
Star Trek.
Yeah, I'm with Leon, this one.
Well, we have many listeners.
How come I cannot say that?
Are you filtering my information?
No.
Sensor.
Sensoring.
Well, you know, Star Trek is this big show.
I'm distracted by the fan in this moment.
Sorry, guys.
You go ahead.
Yeah, the fan is practicing yoga in our studio right now.
Are you stripping?
No.
Yoga, yoga, yoga.
Next.
All right.
For Friday, we're going to be asking somebody to become our girlfriend or slash boyfriend.
Who are you going to ask to?
Can I ask the fan?
Our fan?
You want to ask our fan to become your girlfriend?
Leon wants to become your girlfriend.
Where are you?
Here.
Do you want to be my girlfriend?
Maybe.
All right.
What do you have to offer?
Enough.
All right.
So there can be some tricky language that you have to use whenever you're asking somebody
out on a date or confessing your feelings.
It's not always easy, right?
Okay.
What is this thing?
Feelings.
We have a sample now of the worst five sentences that you can use when you have to ask somebody
out on a date.
Just call me milk.
I'll do your body good.
Your body's name must be Visa because it's everywhere I want to be.
Can I buy you a drink or do you just want the money?
I may not be the best looking guy here, but I'm the only one talking to you.
I'm new in town.
Could I have directions to your house?
All right.
So I hope you enjoyed this week's This Just In.
Is that it?
That's it.
No.
That's it for this week.
Oh, I just remembered, guys, I have to go.
Marco.
Where are you going?
Oh, I have a previous appointment.
I have to go now.
Marco, where are you going?
You look very suspicious.
Okay.
I'll just go now.
And why do you have?
Why do you have luggage?
No, it's okay.
It's okay.
Look, there's a freeze.
Why are you doing with your passport?
Marco.
Where is he going, man?
I don't know.
I hope he'll come back though.
All right.
Anyways.
So this is it, right?
We'll see you guys next time.
All right.
Bye.
EnglishPod.com.